The next brush we are going to discuss is a powder brush.
I'm going to use loose powder today, so I have this loose powder brush.
I call this my Don King brush.
It's very soft and it's a combination of synthetic and natural hair.
This is a great brush for powder because it keeps everything loose without giving it a cakey feel.
Like I said, I'm using a loose powder today, so I want to start by taking some of the powder and pouring it into the cap.
That's good.
I'm going to lightly tap the brush into the powder.
Tap off some of the excess and just lightly go over the entire face.
Under the eye where we just concealed, working my way down and out.
Again, tap, work up toward the hair line.
You always want to work your way toward the hair line.
This is a translucent powder so it's going to give a really light finish and you don't necessarily have to be perfect with it.
I know this is a unique brush.
Everyone might have something closer to this at their house.
You would use it the same way.
Just swirl it in the powder.
You might have to tap it off a little bit because you can see how it gets deposits of more powder whereas this one gets an equal share of powder through the whole brush.